<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<KSPedia xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" Name="deepfreeze" CreatedTime="-8587412490447651862">
  <Categories>
    <Category Name="DeepFreeze">
      <Title>DeepFreeze</Title>
      <TitleScreen>DeepFreezeMain</TitleScreen>
      <Screens />
      <Subcategories>
        <Subcategory Name="Parts">
          <Title>DeepFreeze Parts</Title>
          <TitleScreen>DeepFreezeParts</TitleScreen>
          <Screens />
          <Subcategories />
        </Subcategory>
      </Subcategories>
    </Category>
  </Categories>
  <Screens>
    <Screen Name="DeepFreezeParts">
      <BundleName>deepfreeze</BundleName>
      <AssetPath>Assets/KSPedia/DeepFreezeParts.prefab</AssetPath>
      <Title />
      <Background />
      <Text>
        <Text Name="headingText">
          <Text>DeepFreeze</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextDesc1">
          <Text>The CRY-0300 has animated doors and the CRY-0300R is transparent (with RasterPropMonitor installed). Both can hold One Kerbal and are equipped with one Cryopod. The CRY-0300R can be radially attached.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextDesc2">
          <Text>All DeepFreeze Freezers come with a built-in Glykerol storage tank of various capacities. But the Radial Glykerol Tank allows you to bring along extra Glykerol if required.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextDesc3">
          <Text>The CRY-1300 is a 2.5M Freezer with three Cryopod (kerbal) capacity.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextDesc4">
          <Text>The CRY-2300 is a 2.5M Freeze with ten Cryopod (kerbal) capacity.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextDesc5">
          <Text>The CRY-5000 (4 Cryopod) and the X200 Glykerol Container are actually distributed as part of the KPBS Mod but are DeepFreeze parts (and dependant) made to fit-in and be part of KPBS mod. </Text>
        </Text>
      </Text>
      <Tooltips />
    </Screen>
    <Screen Name="DeepFreezeMain">
      <BundleName>deepfreeze</BundleName>
      <AssetPath>Assets/KSPedia/DeepFreezeMain.prefab</AssetPath>
      <Title />
      <Background />
      <Text>
        <Text Name="headingText">
          <Text>DeepFreeze</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextDescription">
          <Text>DeepFreeze is a Mod that allows you to Freeze Kerbals using the magic of Glykerol and Electricity. Whilst frozen Kerbals will not consume any resources (from Life Support Mods).</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextParts">
          <Text>DeepFreeze Freezer Parts come in a variety of sizes. From the CRY-0300 and CRY-0300R Single Kerbal Freezers right up to the 10 kerbal capacity CRY-2300.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextGUI">
          <Text>The GUI Window allows easy access to monitor all your vessels equiped with DeepFreezer parts and buttons to freeze and thaw your Kerbals.</Text>
        </Text>
      </Text>
      <Tooltips />
    </Screen>
  </Screens>
</KSPedia>