<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<KSPedia xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" Name="deepfreeze" CreatedTime="-8587395526229859482">
  <Categories>
    <Category Name="DeepFreeze">
      <Title>DeepFreeze</Title>
      <TitleScreen>DeepFreezeMain</TitleScreen>
      <Screens />
      <Subcategories>
        <Subcategory Name="Parts">
          <Title>Parts</Title>
          <TitleScreen>DeepFreezeParts</TitleScreen>
          <Screens />
          <Subcategories />
        </Subcategory>
        <Subcategory Name="Settings">
          <Title>Settings</Title>
          <TitleScreen>DeepFreezeSettings</TitleScreen>
          <Screens />
          <Subcategories />
        </Subcategory>
        <Subcategory Name="VesselMenu">
          <Title>VesselMenu</Title>
          <TitleScreen>DeepFreezeVesselMenu</TitleScreen>
          <Screens />
          <Subcategories />
        </Subcategory>
        <Subcategory Name="KACMenu">
          <Title>KACMenu</Title>
          <TitleScreen>DeepFreezeKACMenu</TitleScreen>
          <Screens />
          <Subcategories />
        </Subcategory>
      </Subcategories>
    </Category>
  </Categories>
  <Screens>
    <Screen Name="DeepFreezeVesselMenu">
      <BundleName>deepfreeze</BundleName>
      <AssetPath>Assets/KSPedia/DeepFreezeVesselMenu.prefab</AssetPath>
      <Title />
      <Background />
      <Text>
        <Text Name="TextDesc1">
          <Text>The vessel Menu - Shown by clicking the DeepFreeze Icon.
The top half of the screen shows you all known Vessels that contain DeepFreeze Freezer parts.
If you have set EC usage and/or Temperature usage settings on in the settings menu you will see the Temperature and/or the current EC status of each part in this menu.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextDesc2">
          <Text>EC and Tmp Status Values are colour coded.
If you have Remote Tech mod installed you will also see the Remote Tech status.
If you have Kerbal Alarm Clock installed any Alarms associated with a vessel will show an Alarms Button (see the Alarms KSPedia entry). 
LastUpd - Indicates the last time the vessel was active and had it's EC and temperature actively updated.
TimeRem - Is approx. time remaining for EC based on current Freezer usage.
In the bottom half of the window will be a list of all Kerbals that are on-board a known Freezer in flight. Freeze &amp; Thaw buttons will appear and allow you to Freeze or thaw your kerbals.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextDesc3">
          <Text>Lots of information is displayed about your Freezer in the part right click menu. You can also access the Vessel Menu and Freeze and Thaw your kerbals from here.</Text>
        </Text>
      </Text>
      <Tooltips />
    </Screen>
    <Screen Name="DeepFreezeSettings">
      <BundleName>deepfreeze</BundleName>
      <AssetPath>Assets/KSPedia/DeepFreezeSettings.prefab</AssetPath>
      <Title />
      <Background />
      <Text>
        <Text Name="TextDesc1">
          <Text>The Settings Menu Options In Order:
- If ElectricCharge is required to run Freezers when there are frozen kerbals.
- If on running out of EC or over Temp freezers will kill frozen kerbals.
- If previous is on kerbals will become comatose for this period of time instead of being killed.
- If on frozen kerbals will be thawed out automatically when vessels are recovered.
- If previous is on the cost of funds to thaw each frozen kerbal automatically.
- The amount of ElectricCharge to thaw or freeze a kerbal in flight.
- The amount of Glykerol required to freeze a kerbal in flight.
- If on Temperature regulation of freezer parts is required.
- If previous is on the minimum temperature a freezer must have (internal) in order to freeze a kerbal successfully (temperature can be seen via the DeepFreeze vessel window or via the part right click menu).
- The maximum temperature a freezer can be to maintain frozen kerbals.
- The amount of heat generated by a Cryopod during a thaw or freeze process.
- The amount of heat generated by the Freezer to maintain each frozen kerbal inside.
- If on Temperatures in menus are shown in Kelvin, if off temperatures are show in Celcius.
- If on Stock application launcher Icon is used. If off (and you have it installed) the Toolbar Mod Icons will be used.
- If on strip lights in Freezers (that have them) will animate.
- Spam the log with lots of debug messages (use for capturing logs for reporting problems).
- If on you get lots of tooltips on every DeepFreeze menu item.</Text>
        </Text>
      </Text>
      <Tooltips />
    </Screen>
    <Screen Name="DeepFreezeParts">
      <BundleName>deepfreeze</BundleName>
      <AssetPath>Assets/KSPedia/DeepFreezeParts.prefab</AssetPath>
      <Title />
      <Background />
      <Text>
        <Text Name="headingText">
          <Text>DeepFreeze</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextDesc1">
          <Text>The CRY-0300 has animated doors and the CRY-0300R is transparent (with RasterPropMonitor installed). Both can hold One Kerbal and are equipped with one Cryopod. The CRY-0300R can be radially attached.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextDesc2">
          <Text>All DeepFreeze Freezers come with a built-in Glykerol storage tank of various capacities. But the Radial Glykerol Tank allows you to bring along extra Glykerol if required.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextDesc3">
          <Text>The CRY-1300 is a 2.5M Freezer with three Cryopod (kerbal) capacity.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextDesc4">
          <Text>The CRY-2300 is a 2.5M Freeze with ten Cryopod (kerbal) capacity.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextDesc5">
          <Text>The CRY-5000 (4 Cryopod) and the X200 Glykerol Container are actually distributed as part of the KPBS Mod but are DeepFreeze parts (and dependant) made to fit-in and be part of KPBS mod. </Text>
        </Text>
      </Text>
      <Tooltips />
    </Screen>
    <Screen Name="DeepFreezeMain">
      <BundleName>deepfreeze</BundleName>
      <AssetPath>Assets/KSPedia/DeepFreezeMain.prefab</AssetPath>
      <Title />
      <Background />
      <Text>
        <Text Name="headingText">
          <Text>DeepFreeze</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextDescription">
          <Text>DeepFreeze is a Mod that allows you to Freeze Kerbals using the magic of Glykerol and Electricity. Whilst frozen Kerbals will not consume any resources (from Life Support Mods).</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextParts">
          <Text>DeepFreeze Freezer Parts come in a variety of sizes. From the CRY-0300 and CRY-0300R Single Kerbal Freezers right up to the 10 kerbal capacity CRY-2300.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextGUI">
          <Text>The GUI Window allows easy access to monitor all your vessels equiped with DeepFreezer parts and buttons to freeze and thaw your Kerbals.</Text>
        </Text>
      </Text>
      <Tooltips />
    </Screen>
    <Screen Name="DeepFreezeKACMenu">
      <BundleName>deepfreeze</BundleName>
      <AssetPath>Assets/KSPedia/DeepFreezeKACMenu.prefab</AssetPath>
      <Title />
      <Background />
      <Text>
        <Text Name="TextDesc1">
          <Text>The DeepFreeze Alarms Menu is available if you have also installed the Kerbal Alarm Clock Mod. It can be accessed from the DeepFreeze Vessel Menu (Alarms button at the bottom of the window) at the Space Center or in flight (alarms buttons appear next to the vessels in the list (only if the vessel already has at least one KAC Alarm defined within Kerbal Alarm Clock mod itself.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text Name="TextDesc2">
          <Text>Once you have defined a Kerbal Alarm Clock Alarm that is attached to one of your Deepfreeze equipped vessels you can access the Alarms Menu.
All Alarms will be shown for a vessel when selected and you can then modify each alarm.
For each Alarm you are able to define Thaw and/or Freeze commands for each Kerbal on-board. 
When the KAC alarm is triggered any DeepFreeze commands you have assigned will be executed at that time.
NB: If you have the Remote Tech mod installed you are only able to modify the DeepFreeze commands that are attached to a KAC alarm IF you have active Remote Tech control of that vessel. You do not need control of the vessel for the commands, once defined, to execute when the alarm is triggered.</Text>
        </Text>
      </Text>
      <Tooltips />
    </Screen>
  </Screens>
</KSPedia>